ofoct.com 2015-12-18

# Privacy Policy | Bear File Converter - Online & Free

Privacy Policy

ofoct.com understands the importance of privacy and is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how ofoct.com collects and uses your personal information.

WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?  
ofoct.com collects non-personally identifiable information when you visit our website (www.ofoct.com). This data includes your IP address, the IP address and URL of the Website that sent you to the ofoct.com main page, browser cookie and browser type. This data is automatically recorded in our server logs and is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the ofoct.com website and services.

When you use ofoct.com services, all submitted information, uploaded data and result of usage will be stored on the web server for a maximum of 24 hour exclusively for your convenience.

We will not sell, rent or otherwise distribute your personal information to third parties.

HOW DO WE USE COOKIES?  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

Google is one of the third-pary advertising companies used to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

LINKS TO OTHER SITES  
We may provide links to other websites and products. If you choose to visit a third party website or use its products or services, please be aware that the third party’s privacy policy, not this Privacy Policy, will be in effect. Please review the privacy policies of these sites in order to understand their privacy policies and data collection practices. ofoct.com is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of these websites.
